{
    "id": "bc4d9457dfd74be8b96198f800a58aa9",
    "title": "All and whole | Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9ab9dd865eb849749cc099d01734c2c3",
            "title": "All And Whole",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We canâ€™t spend ................................... time arguing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whole",
                        "the whole",
                        "whole the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why do you argue .......................... time?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "whole",
                        "all the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ thieves have been caught.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "The whole",
                        "Whole",
                        "All the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................. family attended the function.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "All the",
                        "Whole",
                        "The whole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are ................................. responsible for this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whole",
                        "wholly",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have eaten ........................... loaf.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whole",
                        "a whole",
                        "all a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................... London was talking about her affairs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "All the",
                        "The whole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That is ............................. point.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "whole",
                        "the whole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is ....................... in the mind.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "whole",
                        "the whole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I were a millionaire, I would travel ..................... world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "whole",
                        "the whole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}